{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A data warehouse uses:", "opta": "partial operational data.", "optb": "historical operational data.", "optc": "future operational data.", "optd": "health care data.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Metadata enables database designers and users to do all of the following except:", "opta": "sample data.", "optb": "understand what data exist.", "optc": "what the fine distinctions are between similar data items.", "optd": "what the data mean.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Duplicate data often results in loss of data integrity because:", "opta": "the data formats may be inconsistent.", "optb": "data values may not agree.", "optc": "Both A & B.", "optd": "Neither A & B.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Legacy data is which of the following?", "opta": "Data contained in a newly-installed system", "optb": "Data rejected during the installation of a new system", "optc": "Data contained in a file system", "optd": "Data contained by a system used prior to the installation of a new system", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A database management system (DBMS) is a:", "opta": "hardware system used to create, maintain, and provide controlled access to a database.", "optb": "hardware system used to create, maintain, and provide uncontrolled access to a database.", "optc": "software system used to create, maintain, and provide controlled access to a database.", "optd": "software system used to create, maintain, and provide uncontrolled access to a database.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A database application can perform which of the following activities?", "opta": "Add records", "optb": "Read records", "optc": "Update records", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An enterprise data model is:", "opta": "a graphical model that shows the high-level entities for an organization.", "optb": "a graphical model that shows all entities for an organization.", "optc": "a non-graphical model that shows the high-level entities for an organization.", "optd": "a non-graphical model that shows the all entities for an organization.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A shared database should:", "opta": "be accurate and available.", "optb": "provide for backup and recovery.", "optc": "be secure.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Data administrators are responsible for:", "opta": "physical database design.", "optb": "managing technical issues in the database environment.", "optc": "overall management of data resources in an organization.", "optd": "writing application programs.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following types of databases are the most common?", "opta": "Personal", "optb": "Workgroup", "optc": "Department", "optd": "Enterprise", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true for a relational database?", "opta": "Data is represented by tables.", "optb": "It is difficult to access data.", "optc": "Complex programs have to be written for simple queries.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some advantages of the database approach include all, but:", "opta": "minimal data redundancy.", "optb": "improved data consistency.", "optc": "improved data sharing.", "optd": "program-data dependency.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An enterprise database is which of the following?", "opta": "A database designed to support only users external to an organization", "optb": "A database designed to support an entire organization", "optc": "A database designed to support a relatively small group", "optd": "A database designed to support a single PC", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Structured data may include which of the following?", "opta": "Photo image", "optb": "Video clip", "optc": "Dates", "optd": "None of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An extranet is which of the following?", "opta": "The use of Internet protocols with limited access to company data by the company's customers and suppliers.", "optb": "The use of Internet protocols with unlimited access to company data by the company's customers and suppliers.", "optc": "The use of Internet protocols with limited access to company data by people within an organization.", "optd": "The use of Internet protocols with unlimited access to company data by people within an organization.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}